I give the floor to Mr. Tavaresh to move the request, please.
Thank you, President.
Well, some colleagues took the initiative of putting in the agenda an urgency resolution on Brazil's refusal to extradite Cesare Baptista to Italy.
I do understand their motives, but as I shall demonstrate, this is not a present human rights case.
It is not an urgent case, and it is not even a breach of the rule of law case.
Furthermore, it comes at a terrible moment when Brazil is facing the worst natural disaster in its history.
Cesar Abatisi is in prison, is waiting for a decision of the Brazil Supreme Court, and the Supreme Court is in the Holidays of the Southern Hemisphere.
There is no reason to believe that there won't be an independent decision.
I express my solidarity with the families of the victims in this case, and rest assured I have no sympathy towards political violence, either from the right or the left.
But we should use the agencies to debate southern Sudan, the case of Bushar Tabuni in Indonesia, or the Palestinian men shot dead in his bed.
Will the parliament grant President Dilma Rousseff on the very first occasion after her groundbreaking election, and for no sound formal reason, the kind of debate that we usually reserve for people like Mubakabe?
I ask you to remove Brazil from the agenda of the agency.
Thank you very much.
Who would like to speak in favor of this request?
I don't see any comments.
Who wants to speak against this request?
Mr. Mauro.